I will never forget this moment.
A major outage had occurred for a technology company where I was responsible for all of
revenue.
I was new to the company, and we had impacted some of the biggest companies on the planet
where they were not able to do business as promised.
Everyone was scrambling.
No one had a solution.
And I was on vacation with my family.
Here's what I learned about myself.
When life gets difficult, it can be tempting to hide, to shrink, or even to just avoid
the situation, to delegate.
That's not what I did.
And that's not what you should do either.
This crisis was one of those moments where showing up really mattered.
And so I did, from a hotel room, on calls I didn't plan to take, while my family waited
and eventually had to go on without me.
Not because I had the answers, I really didn't.
I found myself hosting hourly calls with my teams, trying to create some kind of rhythm
and order at a time of great uncertainty.
Our customers were rightfully upset, and our teams were so nervous and needed help.
Everyone needs to know at these times that someone is paying attention.
That we were going to keep moving forward one step at a time, even if we didn't have
it all figured out.
We worked around the clock, and eventually everything was back to normal.
We got through it.
What I found so interesting about the outcome of the entire event is that we built stronger
relationships with our clients than ever before as a result of the incident.
We earned their trust by showing up when it mattered most.
And here's the lesson I want you to take with you as you embark on your 90-day journey.
In life, things will go wrong, and when they do, people will want answers.
But if you can't give concrete answers, they expect you at a minimum to remain accessible
and visible.
Consistent communication will never be more important.
And at the end of the day, most people understand that issues will come up.
Every person and every company will have issues at some point.
How you show up in those times makes all the difference, and it's what defines you as a
leader.
Being agile and resilient will never be more important when you're facing big challenges.
So here's my question for you.
How will you show up in times of uncertainty?